(Sheldon:)She was late.
(Sheldon:)And...
(Sheldon:)she found
atomic spectroscopy boring.
(Sheldon:)Well, I wouldn't coitus her
with your genitals.
(Dave:)Uh, thanks
for driving me home.
(Howard:)No problem.
(Amy:)I'm really sorry about your car.
(Dave:)Oh, it's all right.
(Dave:)If you're free next weekend,
I'd love to take you out again.
(Amy:)Um... listen,
you're a really nice guy,
(Amy:)but I just... I don't think
this is working out.
(Dave:)Oh. Okay.
(sighs): I'm...
(Amy:)I'm really sorry.
(Sheldon:)No, it's...
at least the same woman
(Dave:)that rejected Sheldon Cooper
rejected me.
(Amy:)There you go.
(awkward chuckle)
(Dave:)If I ever do meet him,
we'll have that in common.
(Amy:)Sure. Heh.
(Dave:)And... he's kissed you
and I've kissed you,
(Dave:)so if you think about it...
Okay, get out.